Here you go.
Thanks.
You gotta be kidding me.
Sorry?
You're Elon Musk.
I am?
Well, what are you doing here?
I'm washing dishes.
Well, I was on the turkey line,
but I got the motor for being too generous with the gravy.
Oh, man.
I learned an honor to meet you.
I'm such a fan of Tesla and SpaceX,
all your companies of Howard Wallowicz, Caltech.
Nice to meet you, Howard.
I feel great to come down here and help the less fortunate, huh?
Oh, yeah.
It's just nothing better than helping people.
It's just something I realized when I was viewing Earth
from the deck of the International Space Station,
where I spent two months as a payload specialist.
The job I was qualified for, because I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
And I thought I laid off the gravy on pick.
Sorry, it's just you're you.
I really want you to adopt me.
Well, you're here on Thanksgiving, so you're probably a good person.
Oh, I made my wife come down to...
You think you might ever get back out to space?
Is that a job offer?
Because I really want to go to Mars.
Assuming I can bring my wife.
She hardly takes up any room. She's basically a carry-on.
Well, we're not quite there yet, but we're always looking for engineers.
So don't you give me my email, we can stay in touch.
Thank you.
Oh, look. Someone hardly touched their pumpkin pie.
Wanna share it with me?
I've partially eaten piece of pumpkin pie from a homeless shelter
with Elon Musk, you bet I do!